export class Joke {
    question: string;
    answer: string;
}

export const jokes: Joke[] = [
    {question:"What would you get if you crossed a turkey with an ghost?", answer:"A poultrygeist!"},
    {question:"Why did the police arrest the turkey?", answer:"They suspected fowl play."},
    {question:"Why did the turkey cross the road twice?", answer:"To prove he wasn’t a chicken!"},
    {question:"What happened when the turkey got into a fight?", answer:"He got the stuffing knocked out of him!"},
    {question:"What key won’t open any door?", answer:"A turkey!"},
    {question:"What did the mother turkey say to her disobedient children?", answer:"If your father could see you now, he’d turn over in his gravy"},
    {question:"What kind of weather does a turkey like?", answer:"Fowl weather!"},
    {question:"What’s the best dance to do on Thanksgiving?", answer:"The turkey trot."},
    {question:"If you call a large turkey a gobbler what do you call a small one?", answer:"Goblet"},
    {question:"Who is not hungry at Thanksgiving?", answer:"The turkey because he’s already stuffed!"},
    {question:"Why should you never set the turkey next to the dessert?", answer:"Because he will gobble, gobble it up!"},
    {question:"What sound does a turkey’s phone make?", answer:"Wing, Wing! Wing, Wing!"},
    {question:"What’s the most musical part of a turkey?", answer:"The drumstick"},
    {question:"What is a turkey’s favorite dessert?", answer:"Peach gobbler!"},
    {question:"What sound does a limping turkey make?", answer:"Wobble, wobble!"},
    {question:"What do you call it when it rains turkeys?", answer:"Fowl weather!"},
    {question:"What’s the key to a great Thanksgiving dinner?", answer:"The tur KEY."},
    {question:"Why can’t you take a turkey to church?", answer:"They use fowl language."},
    {question:"What is it called when a turkey fumbles in football?", answer:"A fowl play"},
    {question:"Fruit comes from a fruit tree, so where does turkey come from?", answer:"A poul-tree."},
    {question:"Why shouldn’t you look at the turkey dressing?", answer:"Because it will make him blush."},
    {question:"How are a turkey, a donkey, and a monkey alike?", answer:"They all have keys."},
    {question:"Which side of the turkey has the most feathers?", answer:"The outside!"},
    {question:"What do turkeys like to do on sunny days?", answer:"Have peck-nics!"},
    {question:"Why do turkeys lay eggs?", answer:"Because if they dropped them, they would break."},
    {question:"Why did the turkey refuse dessert?", answer:"He was stuffed."},
    {question:"What kind of music did the Pilgrims like?", answer:"Plymouth Rock"},
    {question:"If April showers bring May flowers, what do May flowers bring?", answer:"Pilgrims"},
    {question:"What do you get when you cross a turkey with a banjo?", answer:"A turkey that can pluck itself!"},
    {question:"When do you serve tofu turkey?", answer:"Pranksgiving."},
    {question:"What did the turkey say to the man who tried to shoot it?", answer:"Liberty, Equality and Bad aim for all."},
    {question:"Why did the Pilgrims want to sail to America in the spring?", answer:"Because April showers bring Mayflowers!"},
    {question:"What did baby corn say to mama corn?", answer:"Where's popcorn?"},
    {question:"If the Pilgrims were alive today, what would they be most famous for?", answer:"Their AGE!"},
    {question:"Why do the pants of pilgrims keep falling down?", answer:"Because their belt buckles are on their hats!"},
    {question:"Why did they let the turkey join the band?", answer:"Because he had the drumsticks"},
    {question:"What two animals get stuffed on Thanksgiving?", answer:"Turkeys & people after Thanksgiving dinner."},
    {question:"If a man wants to eat a turkey on Thanksgiving, what does a turkey want?", answer:"It simply wants to run away."},
    {question:"What did the turkeys sing on Thanksgiving Day?", answer:"God save the kin."},
    {question:"Why did the police arrest the turkey?", answer:"They suspected it of fowl play"},
    {question:"What happened to the Pilgrim who was shot at by an Indian?", answer:"He had an arrow escape"},
    {question:"What does a English turkey say to another English turkey on Thanksgiving morning?", answer:"To be or not to be roasted, that is the question."},
    {question:"Why do turkeys always go, gobble, gobble?", answer:"Because they never learned good table manners!"},
    {question:"What sound does a space turkey make?", answer:"Hubble, Hubble, Hubble!"},
    {question:"Why did the turkey cross the road?", answer:"It was the chicken's day off!"},
    {question:"What do you call a running turkey?", answer:"Fast food."},
    {question:"What are the feathers on a turkey's wings called?", answer:"Turkey feathers"},
    {question:"What's the best dance to do on Thanksgiving?", answer:"The turkey trot"},
    {question:"What do you get when you cross a turkey with an octopus?", answer:"Enough drumsticks for Thanksgiving"},
    {question:"What did the turkey say to the computer?", answer:"Google, google, google!"},
    {question:"What do you call the age of a pilgrim?", answer:"Pilgrimage."},
    {question:"What kind of tan did pilgrims get at the beach?", answer:"Puritan."},
    {question:"What do you call a pilgrims vocabulary?", answer:"Pilgrammar."},
    {question:"What was the turkey looking for at Toys are us?", answer:"Gobbleheads."},
    {question:"What does Dracula call Thanksgiving?", answer:"Fangs-giving."},
    {question:"If the pilgrims came on the Mayflower than what does the teacher come on?", answer:"The scholar ships."},
    {question:"In what country is Thanksgiving ironically not celebrated?", answer:"Turkey."},
    {question:"If you call a large turkey a gobbler what do you call a small one?", answer:"Goblet."},
    {question:"What's the best way to stuff a turkey?", answer:"Serve him lots of pizza and ice cream!"},
    {question:"Why did the turkey sit on the tomahawk?", answer:"To hatchet."},
    {question:"What happens to a turkey on Thanksgiving?", answer:"It gets the stuffing knocked in to it."},
    {question:"What do you call a stuffed animal?", answer:"You after thanksgiving."},
    {question:"What smells the best at a Thanksgiving dinner?", answer:"Your nose."},
    {question:"What do you wear to Thanksgiving dinner?", answer:"A Har Vest"},
    {question:"What do you get if you divide the circumference of a pumpkin by its diameter?", answer:"Pumpkin pi."},
    {question:"What is a pumpkin's favorite sport?", answer:"Squash"}
];